Juninho cut his hair at the arroba,
took a look at his hair,
then he did the Hot Wheels track.
it was good bro.
this is key.
as it may be.
and then bro?
,
I'm tough man.
I went to give a workshop yesterday.
I'm speechless.
recorded the deal there.
no, I didn't record.
I did the live one.
oh,
it was live,
it was live.
and today is the seventy-one
coffee
has no?
coffee is over.
Rain is flaming.
i don't know which Way to GO.
Juninho will give me a ride.
I'm out of a car.
Duh, I sold Shell.
want me to do what?
The bank is hot.
Let's go. John
there. oh,
this is partner.
Where didn't the schoolgirl come today?
tamo with hand.
.
it's us huh bro.
Put in gear or.
Juninho leaving.
and then everything is fine people.
is just my turn to smoke,
But i feel Fine.
goodbye dear,
all good.
until the next one.
there
rescue that backpack
and we go there because there are people asking me.
the Cayon
bring the truffles.
I'm taking it.
I told you that I promise the things I bring.
Oh,
I'll give you a better one here.
I'm just going to shoot it so I won't catch you.
It's good here for you too,
my dear.
merry christmas,
all good.
we see each other.
bye bye.
it's bro,
the mall security guards are fine.
and then I had promised them a truffle.
is on
then I just.
deliver the truffle there
that's it right bro?
you have to have a little empathy with people,
right?
know the name,
exchange an idea.
this is what i talked about at the workshop yesterday.
be interesting
is you know how to connect real
with people and not being alone
when you need something.
Is it on?
don't confuse my ability
with my choices,
man.
despite the workshop having worked very well,
that's just a way to get to the point man,
but that will only find out
if you watch till the end bro,
tamo together!